迈克: 嘿,本,既然你非常喜欢的这个艾米女孩同意去看电影,
Mike: Hey Ben, if this Amy girl that you are so hot for already said yes
那么你还有什么问题呢?就是这样!好了,
to the movie, then what's your problem?Yes!Alright, the pressure's on.
压力总是有的,你错过,你就会得C A R O.
You miss this, you've got C A R O.
本:我的问题在于爸妈还从来没有正式说过我可以出去约会.
Ben: My problem is that mum and dad have never really officially said
that I can go out on dates yet.
迈克:但是,我的小球手,
Mike: Yes, my young hornball,
他们也没有正式说过你不能出去约会啊?
but have they officially said that you cannot go out on these dates?
本:是没有.
Ben: No.
迈克:所以你还有问题吗?投这个球,好了,好了,
Mike: So then what's your problem?Shoot the ball.Alright alright.Oh hoo.
哦,你得了C A R O,我只能得C了.行了,我会支持你的.
That's C A R O, and I've only got a C.Ok, here we got.Yes.
本:不,迈克,
Ben: But Mike, mum and dad have got that long standing rule that if you
爸妈制定了标准规定,如果你不问一下的话……
don't ask permission...
迈克:本,本,本,那是针对傻瓜的.
Mike: Bennie, Bennie, Bennie, that's for when toilet roll man walks in the door.
朱莉:晚餐已经好了.
Julie: Your dinner's on.
迈克:好的,我们来问朱莉.
Mike: Alright, let's just ask Julie.
本:决不.
Ben: No way.
朱莉:问我什么?
Julie: Ask me what?
本:没事.
Ben: Nothing.
迈克:关于女孩子.
Mike: It's about girls.
本:迈克!
Ben: Mike!
朱莉:本,你可以问我,我可能比迈克更了解女孩.
Julie: Bennie, you can ask me.I probably know more about girls than Mike does.
迈克:我表示怀疑,我也很精通的.
Mike: I doubt that.And yet I don't.
本:那是男孩子的事.
Ben: Well it's kind of a guy thing.
朱莉:我相信无论迈克说什么,都会是个好建议.
Julie: Well I'm sure that whatever Mike says it will be good advice.
迈克:哦,谢谢你.
Mike: Oh thank you.
朱莉:为什么?
Julie: For what?
迈克:因为你对我的信任.
Mike: For believing in me.
朱莉:为什么不信任?
Julie: What's not to believe in?
本:你真讨厌,你想干嘛呢?
Ben: What the heck was all that crud?
迈克:注意举止,本,投篮,好的,
Mike: Manners Bennie, manners.Shoot the ball.Alright.Oh hoo.
That's C A R O L, that spells Carol, and you lose
本:我不介意.我不介意是否得个开萝尔,
Ben: I don't care.I do not care if I got Carol.
我只想知道怎么才能和艾米约会?
What am I supposed to do about my date with Amy?
迈克:本,我知道,我们让上帝来决定吧.
Mike: Bennie, I know, we'll let God decide.
本:我想他会站在爸妈那一边.
Ben: I think he's going to side with mum and dad.
迈克:不,不,不,
Mike: No, no, no, no.Ben listen.
不.本,听着,如果你投中的话,
If you make the shot, then you go out with Amy.
就去和艾米约会,如果你不能中,那么我和朱莉之间会有一次秘密联系.
And if you don't then, uh, I have a secret relationship with Julie.
本:嗯!
Ben: Uh!
迈克:开个玩笑.好了.
Mike: Just kidding.Alright.
本:好!
Ben: Yeah!
麦琪和杰森:是你啊!
Maggie and Jason: There you are!
迈克:啊!我在做什么呢?我只是找些香肠吃.
Mike: Ahh!What am I panicking for?I'm just getting baloney.
杰森:对不起,迈克,我们以为你是本.
Jason: Sorry Mike, we thought you were Ben.
麦琪:我们有一点不安.
Maggie: We're a little upset.
迈克:嘿,如果我以为我是本的话,我也会有一点难过的.
Mike: Hey if I thought I was Ben then I'd be a little upset too.
杰森:你知道你弟弟在哪吗?
Jason: Well do you know where your brother is?
迈克:已经半夜了,我想他睡觉了.
Mike: Well it's midnight.My guess would be in bed.
杰森:他不在,他溜出去了.
Jason: He's not.He's snuck out.
麦琪:去约会.
Maggie: On a date.
迈克:不!他还小呢.
Mike: No!Well that little hornball.
麦琪:艾米?鲍恩的母亲打电话过来,想找艾米,
Maggie: Amy Bowen's mother called and wanted to talk to Amy.
我说她不在这儿,她说,
I said she's not here.She said, well there must be some mistake.
肯定出了一些问题,所以我去找本谈,你猜我发现了什么?
So I went in to talk to Ben and what do you think I found?
迈克:三只枕头.
Mike: Three pillows.
杰森:两只,你知道这一切吗,迈克?
Jason: Two pillows.What do you know about this Mike?
迈克:我只知道这小家伙违反了标准的西维尔家规矩,
Mike: Look, all I know is that that young lad broke a long standing Seaver
他应该受到严厉的惩罚.
rule, and he should be punished as punished severely.
现在我要吃我的香肠了.
Now I shall enjoy my baloney.
麦琪:他来了.
Maggie: That's him.
迈克:我们要教训教训他.
Mike: Let's get him.
杰森:我们完全清楚你的秘密约会,年轻人.
Jason: We know all about your secret date young man.
迈克:是的.
Mike: Yeah.
开萝尔:对不起,对不起,我应该告诉你们的.
Carol: I'm sorry, I'm sorry.I should have told you.
所有人:开萝尔!
Everyone: Carol!
迈克:竟然是她,太有趣了.
Mike: That's her all right.This is getting good.
杰森:我们以为你四个小时前就上床睡觉了.
Jason: Now we thought you've been in bed the last four hours.
迈克:你究竟和谁约会了?
Mike: Exactly what kind of a date was this?
杰森:你究竟和谁约会了?
Jason: Exactly what kind of a date was this?
开萝尔:只是和学校新来的一个同学.
Carol: Just with a new guy from school.
麦琪:但是你溜出去了,我们没见过他,
Maggie: But you snuck out.We didn't meet him.We didn't know where you were.
我们不知道你去了哪里,你知道这规矩.
You know the rule.
迈克:我信任这规矩.
Mike: Long standing I believe.
麦琪:这儿怎么回事?
Maggie: What is going on here?
我的两个孩子都溜出去了,
I've got two kids who snuck out,
要是剩下的这一个溜出去我还不会如此激动.
and the one who didn't I'm not too thrilled with.
开萝尔:本也出去了?
Carol: Ben snuck out?
杰森:是的.
Jason: Yes.
开萝尔:约会?
Carol: On a date?
麦琪:是的.
Maggie: Yes.
迈克:你认为他是从哪学会这些的?他来了.
Mike: And where do you think he learned such behavior?That's him.
开萝尔:让我们教训教训他.
Carol: Let's get him.
本:嗯,我梦见我想吃东西,于是我醒了,
Ben: Um, I was dreaming about food.I woke up.
穿好衣服,打扮一下,下楼来找吃的.
Got dressed, flipped up my color and came down for a snack.
麦琪:让你一个人来处理这两件事,
Maggie: You really don't feel I'm slothing off my parental duty by having
你不觉得我不就放弃做父母的责任了吗?
you handle both punishments?
杰森:不是这样,你投币赢了.
Jason: No.You won the coin toss far and square.
麦琪:那是你的成人把戏.
Maggie: That's very adult of you.
杰森:本,本,本.
Jason: Ben, Ben, Ben.
本:在,在,在.
Ben: Yes, yes, yes.
杰森:你昨晚的行为是错误的,我们必须随时知道你去了哪儿,
Jason: What you did last night was wrong.
这是不可以商量的.
Now we have to know where you are at all times, and that's not negotiable.
好吧?现在你还有什么好说的?
Alright?Now what do you have to say for yourself?
本:我非常非常爱你们.
Ben: Just that I love you both very very much.
杰森:你不像迈克那样玩花样,但是你出去了,
Jason: You don't have the chops for that Mike stuff, ok.
那会让我担心.
But you're getting there, and that scares me.
本:谢谢你.
Ben: Thank you.
杰森:这可不是表扬你,本,过来,现在我需要你的解释.
Jason: That was not a compliment Ben.Come on, now I want an explanation.
本:艾米?鲍恩太漂亮了,我只是想和她一起出去.我和她就看了一场电影,难道这也不可以吗?
Ben: Any Bowen is so pretty.I just wanted to go out with her.Just her and me for a whole movie.Which by the way was rated G.
杰森:本,
Jason: Well Ben, don't think I don't remember what it's like being a twelve
我想我懂得一个12岁半大的男孩想些什么.
and a half year old boy.
本:我只知道无论什么时候看见艾米的粉红脸蛋上的双眼,
Ben: All I know is that whenever I see Amy shoot those red banks out of
我都会觉得自己要被她的眼神所融化.
her eyes, I just melt.
杰森:雀斑也会造成脸蛋粉红.
Jason: Well there is something about red heads, isn't there.
For me it was freckles.
本:什么?
Ben: What?
杰森:是的,我还记得罗莎琳德?
Jason: Yeah, I can still remember Rosalind Bladder hanging from that jungle
布拉德被绞死在丛林场时,脸上的雀斑还历历在目.
gym.Freckles from here to Tuesday.
本:当你拿一只钢笔时,
Ben: Amy has this really cute way of touching your arm when you're reaching
艾米会用一种非常可爱的方式碰你的胳膊.
for a pencil.
杰森:那可能是无意的.
Jason: Like it was an accident?
本:是的,但是她知道她做了什么.
Ben: Yeah, but she knows she's doing it.
杰森:哦,本,他们都知道.
Jason: Oh Ben, they all know.
本:爸爸,我知道如果我能好好想想的话,
Ben: Dad I know I wouldn't have done any of that bad stuff if I had
我不会做出那么糟糕的举动.
been able to think.
杰森:别这么伤心,本.
Jason: Don't be so hard on yourself Ben.
本:但是我让你们失望了.
Ben: But I disappointed you.
杰森:你只是和一个女孩去看了一场电影,你们只做了这些而已.
Jason: Look, you went to a movie.That's all you did.With a girl.
如果你没有做的话,我倒可能有点失望.
I'd be a little disappointed if you didn't.
本:爸爸,我溜……你接着说.
Ben: Dad, I snuck...go on.
杰森:我想你已经吸取了教训,知道不应该不听我和你妈的话.
Jason: And I think you've learned your lesson about disobeying me and your mum.
本:哦,我知道,我知道.
Ben: Oh I did.I did.
杰森:好了,所以,本,这次给你的惩罚是就是一次严重警告.不过我也希望你保证下不为例,你妈妈很担心.
Jason: Alright.So your punishment this time Ben, is going to be a stern warning.Ok.But I also want you assurance that this won't happen again.Your mother worries.
本:不会了,不会了.
Ben: It won't.It won't.
杰森:好的,嘿,本.出去吧,你这个女生杀手.
Jason: Ok.Hey Ben.Get out of here you lady killer.
杰森:开萝尔,开萝尔,开萝尔.
Jason: Carol, Carol, Carol.
开萝尔:在,在,在.
Carol: Yes, yes, yes.
杰森:我……
Jason: I am...
开萝尔:对我很失望.
Carol: Very disappointed in me.
杰森:你做了……
Jason: What you did...
开萝尔:很糟糕.
Carol: Very wrong.
杰森:是的,如果你不……
Jason: Yes and if you don't...
开萝尔:对我的期望很大.
Carol: Expect so much better form me.
杰森:我要惩罚你,我说一下,好吧.
Jason: I'm doing the punishment.I get to talk, ok.
开萝尔:你说吧.
Carol: Go ahead.
杰森:好.你有要说的吗?
Jason: Ok.What do you have to say for yourself?
开萝尔:我班上有个帅小伙查利,他真的真的很可爱,
Carol: Well see, there's this guy Charlie in my trig class,
害羞.
and he's really really cute.Shy.
所以,当他突然邀请我去看电影的时候……
So when out of the blue he invited me to the movies...
杰森:开萝尔,不管你说什么,
Jason: Is there anything, Carol, in what you are going to say,
都改变不了你违反了西维尔家规矩的事实.
that will change the fact that you broke a long standing Seaver rule?
开萝尔:爸爸,我可以解释为什么悄悄地溜出屋子.
Carol: Dad, I can explain sneaking out of the house.
杰森:我谈的不是那个,
Jason: I'm not talking about that rule.
我谈的是西维尔家的规矩,
I'm talking about the other Seaver rule.
我们必须见一下你的朋友,
We have to meet your friends,
我们必须随时知道你去了哪.
and we have to know where you're going to be at all times.
谢谢你指出你违反了西维尔家的两条规矩.
And thank you for pointing out that you broke two Seaver rules.
开萝尔:我不想违反任何规矩,只是……
Carol: I didn't plan on breaking any rules, it just...
杰森:你做了.
Jason: Happened.
开萝尔:是的,你记得你年轻的时候吗?
Carol: Well yeah.Don't you remember when you were young?
杰森:我记得我很服从父亲的规矩.
Jason: I remember obeying my father's rules.
开萝尔:你从来都没有为一个可爱的人冲昏头脑吗?
Carol: Don't you ever remember losing your head over a really cute guy?
杰森:我想我没有.
Jason: Not that I can recall.
开萝尔:爸爸,我知道那是错的……
Carol: Dad, I know what I did was wrong...
杰森:你早就知道.
Jason: You bet it was.
开萝尔:但是如果……
Carol: But if...
杰森:你知道规矩吗?
Jason: Did you know the rules?
开萝尔:是的.
Carol: Well yes.
杰森:你违反了规矩吗?
Jason: Did you break the rules?
开萝尔:是的……
Carol: Yes...
杰森:你是被强迫的吗?
Jason: Were you under the control of alien beings?
开萝尔:没有!
Carol: Hu!
杰森:那么关你两个星期禁闭.
Jason: No.Then you are grounded for two weeks.
开萝尔:两个星期!爸爸,
Carol: Two weeks!Dad I've learned my lesson.
我吸取教训了.你可以让我办证下不为例.
You have my assurance that this will not happen again.
杰森:等一下,你实际上上次也这么说了,
Jason: Wait a minute.That's exactly what you said the last time this happened.
因此关你一个月禁闭,我们说清楚了吧?
So you are grounded for a full month.Are we clear?
迈克:很好,本!你得了一个警告!当我像你一样大时也和你一样.
Mike: Alright Bennie!You got a warning!You are almost as good as I was when I was your age.
本:那是爸爸说的.
Ben: That's what dad said.
迈克:喔.我被爸爸感动了.
Mike: Wow.I made an impression on the man.
开萝尔:你们这么开心?
Carol: What are you so happy about squirt?
本:我的惩罚.
Ben: My punishment.
开萝尔:像你这样见识比较少的人,
Carol: Yeah, well I guess a month of grounding doesn't mean much to someone
我想关一个月禁闭并没有什么.
with your limited horizons.
迈克:爸爸关了你一个月禁闭?
Mike: Dad grounded you for a month?
开萝尔:嗯.
Carol: Uh hu.
迈克:你知道我越来越尊敬爸爸了.
Mike: You know my respect for that man grows more and more every day.
开萝尔:为什么?你怎么样了,本?
Carol: Why?What did you get Ben?
本:我想我不能告诉你.
Ben: Well, I don't think I should tell you.
开萝尔:说吧,本.你关了多久禁闭?
Carol: Come on Ben.How long were you grounded for?
本:好的……
Ben: Well...
开萝尔:两个星期?
Carol: Two weeks?
本:不是……
Ben: Uh...
开萝尔:一个星期?
Carol: One week?
本:不准确.
Ben: Not exactly.
开萝尔:那是什么?
Carol: What what?
迈克:嘿嘿,很出人意料,他给了本一个警告.
Mike: Hey hey.Get off his back.He got a warning.
开萝尔:一个警告!一个该死的警告!
Carol: A warning!A stinking warning!
本:因为我已经保证不会再犯了.
Ben: Plus my word that I would never do it again.
开萝尔:不好意思,我要脱了我的袜裤.
Carol: Well pardon me while I pop my pantyhose.
本:嘿,我只违反了爸妈的一条规矩.
Ben: Hey, all I really did was break one of mum and dad's rules.
开萝尔:两条,我做的和你这小兔崽子一样.
Carol: It's two rules, and I did the same thing you little rodent.
迈克:嘿,
Mike: Hey, I believe calling your brother a furry little animal violates
我想你骂你弟弟小兔崽子违反了西维尔家的第六条规矩.
Seaver rule number six.
开萝尔:我揍你.
Carol: Pus bag.
迈克:嗯,第七条.
Mike: Uh hu.Seaver rule seven.
本:嘿,迈克,你来吗?我和爸爸要去看尼克斯队的比赛了.
Ben: Hey Mike.Are you coming?Me and dad are going to watch the Nicks game.
迈克:好的,等一会.
Mike: Yeah.In a minute.
开萝尔:我一点都不能接受.
Carol: I do not get this at all.
迈克:不过开萝尔,很明显你忘了最重要的一点.
Mike: Well then obviously Carol, you are missing a very important point.
开萝尔:什么?
Carol: What?
迈克:你是女孩,本尽管年纪很小,但他是个男孩.
Mike: Well that you are a girl and Ben is, although a small one, a guy.
开萝尔:那是性别歧视.
Carol: That's sexism.
迈克:嘿,开萝尔.
Mike: Hey look Carol.
如果你对此反应强烈的话,那么你就别再剃你的腋毛了.
If you feel that strongly about it, just stop shaving your armpits.
开萝尔:妈妈!
Carol: Mum!
麦琪:开萝尔,向我申诉对你的惩罚,
Maggie: Carol, it won't do you any good to appeal your punishment to me.
不会对你任何好处,你爸爸讲的话代表我们两个人.
Your father spoke for both of us.
开萝尔:妈妈,有件事我必须告诉你.
Carol: Mother, there is something I must tell you.
在我们中间有人有性别歧视.
There is a sexist male in out midst.
麦琪:是迈克对你说了什么卑劣的话吧?
Maggie: What sleazy thing did Mike say to you?
开萝尔:妈妈,我说的是一只更大的猪,就是你嫁的那个男人.
Carol: Mum, I'm talking about a bigger pig.A man you married.
麦琪:开萝尔,你太无礼了.没人可以说你爸爸是猪,除了我.
Maggie: Carol, that is very disrespectful.No one calls your dad a pig, but me.
电视:尤因投篮.好!
TV: Ewing shoots.Yeah!
本,迈克和杰森:好!
Ben, Mike and Jason: Yeah!
麦琪:杰森宝贝,你有时间吗?
Maggie: Jason honey, have you got a second?
杰森:我在,等一会,宝贝.尼克斯队落后两分,比赛只剩最后一分钟了.
Jason: Yeah, in a minute honey.Nicks are down by two.Last minute of the game.
麦琪:开萝尔有意见……
Maggie: See Carol has this silly idea that...
杰森:他进了!
Jason: He's done it!
本,迈克和杰森:好!
Ben, Mike and Jason: Yeah!
电视:带球,带球,好!
TV: Driving, driving, yeah!
迈克:是的,被阻挡了.
Mike: Yes, it's all tied up.
麦琪:哦,你就像没有受过惩罚一样.
Maggie: Oh, this is almost as good as you getting off with no punishment.
本:你说的对.
Ben: You said it.
麦琪:杰森.
Maggie: Jason.
杰森:好,等下一个广告时间吧,宝贝.
Jason: Yeah, the next commercial honey.
电视:他得到球,带球沿着边线往前冲,他投篮了,球进了.
TV: He's got it.He's making a dribble drive down the lane.This could be the game.He shoots and it's in.
本,迈克,杰森:啊!
Ben, Mike, Jason: Ahhh!
麦琪:是广告时间了.
Maggie: The next commercial is here.
杰森:麦琪,什么事?我们在看尤因带球呢!
Jason: Maggie, what is it?We got Ewing dribble driving down the lane here!
麦琪:电视真的要比家庭生活更重要吗?
Maggie: Is television really more important than family life?
本:对于我来说是.
Ben: It is to me.
麦琪:本,现在回你的房间.
Maggie: Ben, go to your room now.
迈克:我也去.
Mike: Look, I'm going too.
爸爸,我不知道你违反了哪条西维尔家规矩,
And dad look, I don't know what Seaver rule you broke,
但是你陷入一个大大的麻烦了.
but you are in big big trouble.
麦琪:迈克,我们只是要简单的讨论一下.
Maggie: Mike we are just going to have a simple discussion.
迈克:好的,但是爸爸我给你一条建议,记住你是一个男人.
Mike: Alright.But just one word of advice for you dad.Remember you're a man.
杰森:我知道迈克.我只是开玩笑,麦琪,我是开玩笑.什么事情这么重要?
Jason: I know that Mike.I'm kidding Maggie, I'm kidding.Well what is so important?
麦琪:杰森,宝贝,
Maggie: Jason honey, I think you've sent the wrong message with these
我想你在宣布这些惩罚时你传达了一些错误信息.
punishments you've handed out.
杰森:什么信息?
Jason: What message?
麦琪:我有点不好意思说,
Maggie: Well I'm a little embarrassed to say,
开萝尔认为她受惩罚了,而本没有,
but carol thinks that the reason she was punished and Ben wasn't,
是因为你有性别歧视.
is because you're sexist.
杰森:那完全是错误的.
Jason: Well it's totally wrong.
麦琪:我知道.
Maggie: I knew it was.
杰森:我希望你理解,真的.
Jason: I should hope so.Yes.
麦琪:我告诉她这完全是一个误会,
Maggie: I told her it was all a misunderstanding and I knew you had very
我知道你有充分的理由给出不同的惩罚.
good reasons for giving out different punishments.
杰森:你说的很对.
Jason: You bet I did.
麦琪:那是什么呢?
Maggie: What were they?
杰森:你现在就想听吗?
Jason: You want to hear them now?
麦琪:哦,不,不.我不需要听.
Maggie: Oh no, no.I don't need to hear them
TV: This is the most incredible game in the history of the MBA.These two
麦琪:只是怕万一开萝尔问我,所以我应当知道.
Maggie: Just incase Carol asks me, I should know.
杰森:好,对于开萝尔这件事,她是知道这些规矩的,
Jason: Ok, well in Carol's case,
但是她溜出去了,去约会一个我们没有见过的男孩.
she knew the rules but she snuck out anyway with a boy we'd never met.
对吧?这还是她第二次违反规矩,所以我要双倍惩罚
Alright?It was her second offence that's why I doubled the grounding.
麦琪:嗯
Maggie: Uh hu.
杰森:对于本这件事,他是一个小孩子.他正处于发育阶段,
Jason: Now in Ben's case, he's a young lad.He's got those raging hormones.
看见漂亮女孩,难免会头脑发热,所以谁能责怪他呢?
He sees a pretty girl and he lost his head, so who can blame him?
麦琪:嗯.你有没有告诉过本,
Maggie: Uh hu.Did you mention it to Ben that he's still six months away
他还有六个月才能出去约会呢?
from being old enough to date?
杰森:没有很明确,但是我……
Jason: Not specifically no, but I...
麦琪:你对他说,他溜出去了,
Maggie: Did you tell him that his sneaking out caused us both to walk
这让我们心神不定,非常担心吗?
the floor with worry?
杰森:说的很婉转,是的,我提出了核心问题……
Jason: In a round about way.Yes I brought up that the core issue here...
麦琪:你注意到有些事必须要直截了说明吗?
Maggie: Did you mention anything specifically in a non round about way?
杰森:我是说了一些.
Jason: I certainly did.Sort of.
麦琪:比如?
Maggie: Like what?
杰森:我告诉他我们对你很担心,我就是这么说的,
Jason: Well I, I told him you were worried.Those were my exact words.
我说你妈妈很担心.
I said your mother is worrying.
麦琪:杰森,你扪心自问一下.
Maggie: Jason, listen to yourself.
杰森:宝贝,你什么意思?
Jason: Honey, what's your point?
麦琪:我想本逃脱惩罚是因为他是一个男孩.
Maggie: I think that Ben got off easy because he's a guy.
杰森:我不喜欢你这样指责我.
Jason: I don't like what you are accusing me of.
麦琪:我不觉得有什么不好.
Maggie: Well I don't feel so hot myself.
杰森:行了,你还记得你烧胸罩的那些日子吗?
Jason: Come on.Don't you remember back in the days when you were burning bras?
我总是拿着一整盒的火柴.现在你却嘲笑.
I was always there with a full box of matches.You'll laugh later.
麦琪:杰森,我真不知道说什么.
Maggie: Jason, I don't know what to say.
杰森:宝贝,我想你把事情看得太简单了.
Jason: Honey, I think you are just looking at this in very simplistic terms.
麦琪:简单?
Maggie: Simplistic?
杰森:我说了什么做了什么并没有关系,
Jason: It doesn't matter what I say or do right now, does it?
你要坚持的却是不合逻辑的惯例.
You are going to be stuck there in this illogical rut.
麦琪:不合逻辑的惯例?
Maggie: Illogical rut?
杰森:哦,我可能用词不当,我很抱歉.
Jason: Oh my choice of words may not be ideal.I'm sorry.
麦琪:但是你意思是什么呢?
Maggie: But isn't that what you meant?
杰森:你为什么那样说?指责我是一个有性别歧视的人.
Jason: Why are you offended?I'm the one being accused of being a sexist.
麦琪:你这是胡说.
Maggie: If the snout fits, wear it.
杰森:如果你不认为我可以公平地处理惩罚,你为什么同意掷硬币呢?
Jason: Well then if you didn't think that I could handle the punishment
麦琪,你来吧.
fairly, why did you agree to coin flip?Maggie please.Come down here.
到这儿来,我们都应当冷静一下.
Both of us, we should just calm down.
麦琪:哦,你忘了我是一个头脑简单,不合逻辑,因循守旧的女性了吗?
Maggie: Oh, and forget that I'm a simplistic illogical female stuck in a rut.
杰森:我只是随便说说.
Jason: I'm game if you are.
麦琪:本,本,本.
Maggie: Ben, Ben, Ben.
本:在,在,在.
Ben: Yes, yes, yes.
麦琪:你知道家里的规矩吗?
Maggie: You know the rules of the house?
本:是的,我想其中之一是,
Ben: Yeah, and I thought one of them was that you couldn't get tried for
你不能两次犯同样的错误.
the same crime twice.
麦琪:不,本,那是美国,这是西维尔家.
Maggie: No Ben, that's the United States.This is Seaver land.
本:但是妈妈.艾米?
Ben: But mum, Amy Bowen is so pretty,
鲍恩太漂亮了,
I mean I just wanted to go out with her.
我只想和她一起出去.你知道这对于一个12岁大的男孩意味着什么吗?
Don't you remember what its like to be a twelve year old boy?
麦琪:不,我知道.
Maggie: Not that I recall.
哦,本,
Oh Ben, does anything that you are about to say change the fact that you
无论你怎么说,都改变不了你违反了西维尔家的三条规矩.
broke three long standing Seaver rules?
本:三条!
Ben: Three!
麦琪:第一,你溜出去了;第二,
Maggie: You snuck out.
你和一个我们没见过的人约会;第三,你还不到约会的年龄.
You met a date we didn't know and you're not old enough to date.
本:情况变得越来越糟了,我只好接受了.
Ben: This is getting worse and worse and I'm just standing here.
麦琪:听着,本,现在宣布对你的惩罚:一个月不许看电视.
Maggie: Save it Ben, now for your punishment.No TV for a month.
(一个月都不能看)
(Growing pains will not be seen for a month)
(因为本搞糟了)
(Because Ben messed up)
本:哦,不!
Ben: Oh no!
麦琪:明天开始.
Maggie: Starting tomorrow.
本:少一些!
Ben: Few!
开萝尔:,妈妈,妈妈,妈妈.
Carol: Mum, mum, mum.
麦琪:开萝尔,安静.我要说话.
Maggie: Carol, be quiet.I'm going to do the talking.
开萝尔:对不起.
Carol: Sorry.
麦琪:你在想什么?我得指望你,因为你是我的女儿.
Maggie: What were you thinking?I count on you, you're my daughter.
开萝尔:我知道.
Carol: I know.
麦琪:我希望只有男孩子才会耍些花招,而你不会!
Maggie: I expect these kind of shenanigans from the boys, but you!
开萝尔:妈妈,我昏了头.昨天当查利要我出去……
Carol: Mum, I lost my head.Yesterday when Charlie asked me out...
麦琪:查利?马金利?
Maggie: Charlie Maginly?
开萝尔:嗯.
Carol: Uh hu.
麦琪:你班上的?
Maggie: From trig class?
开萝尔:嗯.
Carol: Uh hu.
麦琪:就是你说的穿牛仔裤的那个小子?
Maggie: The cute one you told me about with the jeans?
开萝尔:就是他.
Carol: That's the one.
麦琪:喔.
Maggie: Wow.
开萝尔:我知道,总之,
Carol: I know.Well anyway, when he asked me out yesterday,
昨天当他要我出去,我很怕告诉你,我是说,
I was afraid to tell you.
这家伙太帅了,爸爸讨厌这样的人.
I mean, this guy is so cute, dad would have hated him for sure.
麦琪:帅的人?
Maggie: That cute hu?
开萝尔:帅哥.总之,
Carol: Cuter.Well anyway, you know,
你知道,好几个星期,
I've been flirting with him for weeks to ask me out.
我都一直希望他会邀请我出去,当然我没有过分主动,
But not too much, because I didn't want him to think that I was a tease.
因为我不想让他认为我很轻佻,另一方面,
But on the other hand,
我也不想让他认为我很冷冰冰.哦,
I didn't want him to think that I was a cold fish.
妈妈,17岁的年龄总是这么苦恼.
Oh mum, being seventeen can be so horrible.
麦琪:哦,宝贝.
Maggie: Oh honey.
开萝尔:你知道,我认为查利可能对我有意思,因为我注意到他总是把鞋子挂在我的储物柜上,雪莉对我说,那不是偶然,他那样做是故意的.
Carol: You know, I thought that Charlie might be interested in me when I noticed that he always seemed to be tying his shoe by my locker.When then shelly said it wasn't an accident and he knew what he was doing.
麦琪:开萝尔,他们都知道.
Maggie: Carol, they all know.
开萝尔:妈妈,他穿运动衣的时候非常迷人.
Carol: And mum, he looks so adorable in his gym shorts.
麦琪:哦,运动衣.我曾经对你说过克拉德?泰勒吗?
Maggie: Oh those gym shorts.Did I ever tell you about Clud Tyler?
开萝尔:没有.
Carol: No.
麦琪:他是篮球队的,我是一名拉拉队员,
Maggie: Well he was on the basketball team, and I was a cheerleader.
整个高中我们一直在一起.高中毕业就分开了,
We went steady all senior year.I dumped him after graduation.
我再也没有见过他,不过我永远记得他的那些运动衣.
He didn't have a lot upstairs, but, uh, I'll never forget those gym shorts.
开萝尔:妈妈,妈妈.
Carol: Mum, mum.
麦琪:哦,对.
Maggie: Oh yes.
(迈克吻了朱莉)
(Mike kisses Julie)
朱莉:你好,本.
Julie: Hi Ben.
迈克:什么?
Mike: What?
朱莉:你.
Julie: Got ya.
迈克:你星期六在这儿做什么呢?
Mike: What the heck are you doing here on Saturday?
朱莉:我不能不来.
Julie: I couldn't stay away.
迈克:哦.
Mike: Oh.
本:傻瓜.
Ben: Nuts.
迈克:白面包,黑面包.
Mike: White bread.Rye bread.
朱莉:怎么了,本?
Julie: Uh, what's the matter Bennie?
本:妈妈比爸爸还厉害,我一个月不能看电视了.
Ben: Mum over ruled dad, and I got a month of no TV.
电视:我们要进行第三次加时,我不知道你们怎么样,但是疯狂的对手不能把我们拉开.接下来,采访……
TV: We're going in to triple overtime.I don't know about you, but mad dogs couldn't drag me away from this one.This...Coming up next, an interview with...
杰森:你开心吗?
Jason: Are you happier?
麦琪:非常开心.
Maggie: Much.
电视:我们将知道简的职业生涯是否会结束,还是继续下去.
TV: We are going to find out if Jane's career is over, or just on hold.
麦琪:我们不能看尼克斯队的比赛吗?
Maggie: Can't we watch the Nicks game?
开萝尔:朱莉.你在这做什么?
Carol: Julie, what are you doing here?
朱莉:只是把这些吃的放下,我要走了.
Julie: Oh, just dropping off the groceries.I got to run.
开萝尔:哦,你有约会吗?
Carol: Oh, you got a date?
朱莉:有.我希望他八点左右来接我,我们可能看些电视,定了一份中餐吃.
Julie: Kind of.Well I was hoping this guy would drop over around eight, and we'll probably watch some TV and order in Chinese.
迈克:听起来真好.
Mike: Sounds like fun.
朱莉:再见.
Julie: Bye.
开萝尔:再见,我今晚也可能出去约会.
Carol: Bye.Yeah well, I might go out on a date myself tonight.
本:等一下,你得到什么惩罚了?
Ben: Wait a minute, what happened to your punishment?
开萝尔:我正在做.
Carol: I'm doing it.
迈克:什么,他们让你走来走去,像个傻瓜一样?
Mike: What, they are making you walk around with a goofy look on your face?
开萝尔:说实话,我得洗一星期早餐盘子.
Carol: For your information, I have to do breakfast dishes all week.
本:本来就是你洗.
Ben: It was your week anyway.
开萝尔:嗯.
Carol: Uh hu.
本:就是这?这就是妈妈给你的?
Ben: That's it?That is all mum gave you?
我一个月不看电视?
And I got a month of no TV?
麦琪:快,快,投篮,投篮!
Maggie: Go, go, shoot it, shoot it!
杰森:你给了本什么惩罚?
Jason: So, what did you give Ben?
麦琪:下一个广告时间再说.喔,好一个回弹球.
Maggie: Next commercial.Wow, great rebound.
杰森:麦琪,电视真的要更重要……
Jason: Maggie, is TV really more important than...
麦琪:投得真漂亮!嘿,你们傻了?他们已经是第四次加时了.
Maggie: What a shot!Hey, are you nuts?They're in quadruple overtime.
杰森:我只是想知道你是如何挽救这形势的,亲爱的,
Jason: Well I merely wanted to see how you remedied the situation dear,
这样我可以学会以后成为一个更好的父母.
so I can learn to become a better parent in the future.
本:这是我听说的最不公平的.
Ben: That is the most unfair thing I've ever heard.
迈克:如果我是你,本,
Mike: If I were you Bennie boy, I would not stand for this.
我不能忍受这些,我闻出了性别歧视的味道.
I know sexism when I smell it.
开萝尔:我也是.它闻起来像廉价的科隆香水.
Carol: Me too.It smells like cheap cologne.
杰森:我是说,
Jason: Well my point is,
你的惩罚可能对孩子们传达了错误信息.
is that maybe your punishment gave out children the wrong message.
麦琪:什么?
Maggie: What?
杰森:是的.有个母亲给了她的女儿某种待遇.
Jason: Yeah.That certain mothers can give certain daughters certain breaks.
麦琪:哦,杰森,你叫我什么,麦琪?马隆太太还是性别歧视者?
Maggie: Oh Jason, are you accusing me, Ms Maggie Malone, or sexism?
杰森:如果胸罩适合的话,烧了它.
Jason: If the bra fits, burn it.
麦琪:哦,杰森,
Maggie: Oh Jason, you can't help but feel this way.
你不能这样以为.我是说,你因为自己的思想狭隘而使得你看不清.
I mean, you're just blinded by your own narrow mindedness.
杰森:思想狭隘?
Jason: Narrow-mindedness?
麦琪:也许我的话很准确.
Maggie: Possibly my choice of words was perfect.
杰森:那是难以置信的,你甚至不知道你错了.
Jason: That's incredible.You don't even know how wrong you are.
麦琪:是你不处罚你的儿子.
Maggie: Didn't you let your son off Scot free?
杰森:是你不处罚你的女儿.
Jason: Didn't you let your daughter off Scot free.
麦琪:我只是理解了我的女儿,因为我知道对于一个17岁的少女,
Maggie: Well I just gave my daughter a little understanding because I
和男孩子接受同样的处分是多么的残酷.
know how tough it is to be seventeen, female, and dealing with boys.
杰森:我也能理解一个男孩有一天突然醒来,发现自己不朽的灵魂,
Jason: And I know how confusing it is to be a boy who suddenly wakes up
只是为了等待一个长满雀斑的女孩,
one day and finds he would trade his immortal soul just for a nice view
这会有多么的痛苦.我说得够清楚了.
of freckles.I can't say it any clearer.
麦琪:杰森,
Maggie: Jason, can't you even consider the possibility that you were easier
你甚至没想到你对本要比开萝尔偏心.
on Ben than Carol?
杰森:当然我是.
Jason: Of course I was.
麦琪:什么?
Maggie: What?
杰森:不是因为我是一个性别歧视者,麦琪,
Jason: Not because I'm sexist Maggie.It's just common knowledge.
这只是个简单的知识,父母总是对女儿要比对儿子更严格.
Both parents are always much tougher on daughters than sons.
麦琪:哦,那不是常识.
Maggie: Oh it's not common anything.
杰森:那应该是.
Jason: Well it should be.
麦琪:男人都是捣蛋鬼,这就是我为什么对本这么严格的原因.
Maggie: Men are such jerks.That's why I was so tough on Ben.
杰森:麦琪,扪心自问一下.
Jason: Maggie, listen to yourself.
麦琪:我知道,我的性别歧视不会比你严重.
Maggie: Well I do know this, I am no more sexist than, than...
杰森:我更严重?
Jason: Than I am?
麦琪:是的.
Maggie: Yes.
杰森和麦琪:哦,天!
Jason and Maggie: Oh Boy!
杰森:你想抱一个性别歧视者吗?
Jason: You want to hug a sexist?
麦琪:你呢?
Maggie: Do you?
杰森:我想.
Jason: I'm thinking.
杰森:因此我们想和你们谈谈关于改善惩罚待遇.
Jason: So we want to talk to you about improving the punishment situation.
本:这正是我想和你们说的.
Ben: That's exactly what I wanted to talk to both of you about.
开萝尔:好的,我想事情应该完满的结束了.
Carol: Well I, for one, think things have gone wonderfully.
麦琪:我们在谈论偏心.
Maggie: We're talking about injustice.
迈克:哦,给我个座.
Mike: Oh, let me get a good seat.
杰森:和你没关系,迈克.
Jason: Doesn't really concern you Mike.
迈克:嘿,你们很认真吗?偏心任何情况下都会关系到我.
Mike: Hey, are you serious?Injustice anywhere concerns me.
杰森:从现在开始,我来负责处理对开萝尔的惩罚.
Jason: From now on, I will be handling all of Carol's punishments.
本:好的!
Ben: Alright!
麦琪:我来负责对本的惩罚.
Maggie: And I will be handling all of Ben's punishments.
开萝尔:好!
Carol: Alright!
迈克:看来你们没有一个会逃脱惩罚.
Mike: Neither of you are going to get away with anything.
本和开萝尔:真是如此!
Ben and Carol: That's right!
杰森:从现在开始,在西维尔家,
Jason: From now on in Seaver land,
你们的妈妈和我将利用我们的性别歧视做一些有益的事,而不是相反.
your mother and I will use our sexism for good, instead of for evil.
开萝尔:喔呜!
Carol: Whoopee!
麦琪:因此,本,你一个月不看电视.
Maggie: So Ben, your month of no TV stands.
杰森:开萝尔,你关一个月禁闭.
Jason: Carol, your month of grounding stands.
开萝尔:但是……
Carol: But...
迈克:嘿,如果你问我,你们两个处分都太轻,尤其是你,开萝尔,每个人都知道女孩应该比男孩更好,对吧,爸爸?
杰森:我不发表意见.
00:21:58,600
Mike: Hey, if you ask me, the two of you are getting off easy.Especially you Carol.Everybody knows that girls are supposed to be better than boys.Right dad? Jason: I'm not saying anything.